Guide to the Sir George Hubert Wilkins Papers
The Ohio State University. Byrd Polar and Climate Research Center Archival Program.
- Series VII: Navigational, 1913-1958; 39 c.f.
  - Arctic Expeditions with Arctic Ocean Floor on Reverse, 1971; 19x24 (Box OV-9, Folder 37)
  - Clear Plastic Map of Canada, Undated (Box OV-9, Folder 38)
  - The Arctic Regions, National Geographic Magazine with Expedition Sites (2 copies), 1925 (Box OV-9, Folder 39)
  - The Arctic Regions, National Geographic Magazine with Expedition Sites, (2 copies), 1925 (Box OV-9, Folder 40)
  - Department of the Naval Service Key Map of Canadian Arctic Expedition Discoveries in the Arctic Sea, 1913-18; 29x24 (Box OV-9, Folder 41)
  - Discoveries in the Arctic Sea, with Added Sketches, 1902; 40x24 (Box OV-9, Folder 42)
  - North Coast of Canada and Arctic Archipelago, including the North-West Passage, 1926; 40x54 (Box OV-9, Folder 43)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 44)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 45)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 46)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 47)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 48)
  - Navigational Chart of the Arctic Basin, (6 copies, 2 of which have sketches), 1926 (Box OV-9, Folder 49)
  - The Arctic Sea North of Canada by American Geographical Society of New York for Sir Hubert Wilkins, (3 copies with sketches, one of which has an additional card attached to it with directional data), 1937 (Box OV-9, Folder 50)
  - The Arctic Sea North of Canada by American Geographical Society of New York for Sir Hubert Wilkins, (3 copies with sketches, one of which has an additional card attached to it with directional data), 1937 (Box OV-9, Folder 51)
  - The Arctic Sea North of Canada by American Geographical Society of New York for Sir Hubert Wilkins, (3 copies with sketches, one of which has an additional card attached to it with directional data), 1937 (Box OV-9, Folder 52)
  - Arctic Institute of North American Field Projects Summer Season, 1947 (Box OV-9, Folder 53)
  - Soviet Search Expedition Approximate Courses, 1937-38 (Box OV-9, Folder 54)
  - Map of Ocean Expedition from England to Antarctica, ca 1921-22; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 55)
  - Map of Ocean Expedition from England to Antarctica, ca 1921-22; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 56)
  - Map of Ocean Expedition from England to Antarctica, ca 1921-22; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 57)
  - Navigational Chart of the Antarctic, 1928; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 58)
  - Navigational Chart of the Antarctic, 1928; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 59)
  - Navigational Chart of the Antarctic, 1928; 22x22 (Box OV-9, Folder 60)
  - (Title in Russian), Physical Map of Polar Region (2 sheets, second sheet has no title), 1940; 20x38 (Box OV-10, Folder 1)
  - R le Societa' Geografica Italiana Diploma Di Medaglia D'Oro Sir George H. Wilkins, 1931 (Box OV-10, Folder 2)
  - George Hubert Wilkins ague su nombre perdure en Los Angeles de la Sociedad Geografica de Cuba, Gran Medalla de Oro, 1929 (Box OV-10, Folder 3)
  - North Polar Map on Board, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 4)
  - Greenwich Date and Hour Scales for use with Gatty's Combined World and Star Chart, 1943 (Box OV-10, Folder 5)
  - The New Matthew-Northrup Global Atlas of the World at War, ca 1943 (Box OV-10, Folder 6)
  - Queensland Four Mile Maps, Sheet 21B, 1910; 40x30 (Box OV-10, Folder 7)
  - CVMBRIA Sive CVMBERLANDIA Quaeolim pars Brigantum, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 8)
  - Ocean Surface Temperatures, February, McKnight and McKnight, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 9)
  - US Army Air Forces Political and Time Chart, GH-1, Northern Hemisphere, 1947; 36x36 (Box OV-10, Folder 10)
  - American Airlines System Map of US and Mexico, Undated; 24x34 (Box OV-10, Folder 11)
  - Coastal Landforms of the World, John T McGill, 1958; 57x35 (Box OV-10, Folder 12)
  - Daily Minimum Water Requirements for Hottest Month, Maps of: Northern Africa, July; India, May; Asia, July; Australia, January; Western US, July, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 13)
  - Palisade Glacier, Sierra Nevada, CA, 1946 (Box OV-10, Folder 14)
  - Teleport-device Used to Find Time and Distance Throughout the World, 1941 (Box OV-10, Folder 15)
  - The Panama Canal Maps of the Canal Zone and Vicinity, 1938 (RV 1947); 40x33 (Box OV-10, Folder 16)
  - North America, The National Geographic Magazine, 1942; 27x33 (Box OV-10, Folder 17)
  - Ocean Surface Temperatures of the World for February (6 copies), 1943 (Box OV-10, Folder 18)
  - Global Air Maps of WWII, North and South Hemisphere, Air Routes of Attack and Defense (3 copies), 1943; 14x28 (Box OV-10, Folder 19)
  - Norges Automobil-Forbund's Bilkary for Gjennemgangstrafikken, 1937; 25x24 (Box OV-10, Folder 20)
  - Northeastern United States, Showing Relation of Land and Submarine Topography, 1939; 36x36 (Box OV-10, Folder 21)
  - Central Europe and the Mediterranean, 1939; 27x36 (Box OV-10, Folder 22)
  - US Department of Commerce Daily Weather Map, June 25, 1947; 19x24 (Box OV-10, Folder 23)
  - Map of Mount Desert Island, Maine, Showing Acadia National Park, 1934; 30x24 (Box OV-10, Folder 24)
  - Plant Transformations of Macquarie Island, Undated; 12x28 (Box OV-10, Folder 25)
  - Summer Time Table of European Airlines, Deutsche Lufthansa, 1938; 33x23 (Box OV-10, Folder 26)
  - US Air Force Economic Chart GH-8 Northern Hemisphere, 1948; 36x36 (Box OV-10, Folder 27)
  - Map of Northern Hemisphere, North of 39 Degree 30 Minutes, Showing Topography, 1945; 52x39 (Box OV-10, Folder 28)
  - Sketch of Zones in Asia, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 29)
  - Map of Dominion of Canada Political and Map of North America on Reverse Side, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 30)
  - Hvalfanger (ship) Blueprint, 1925 (Box OV-10, Folder 31)
  - Map of the Hurricane Alley, 1947-1956 (Box OV-10, Folder 32)
  - Map of the Historic and Scenic Reaches of the Nation's Capital, 1938; 32x27 (Box OV-10, Folder 33)
  - Monthly Variation in Daylight and Darkness at Certain Latitudes, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 34)
  - Monthly Variation in Daylight and Darkness at Certain Latitudes, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 35)
  - "International Map of the World - Index of Sheets", 1936; 16x29 (Box OV-10, Folder 36)
  - Map of "Corn Wall": By Robert Morden, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 37)
  - Map of "Glocestershire": By Robert Morden, Undated (Box OV-10, Folder 38)
  - Map of the Two Hemispheres, Undated; 29x21 (Box OV-10, Folder 39)
  - Small Drawing of Map of Temple Bay, Australia, Undated (Box OV-11, Folder 26)
  - Map of Queensland, Australia: Railway System and Distribution of Livestock, 1920; 18x28 (Box OV-11, Folder 27)
  - "General Map of the Northern Territory", Australia (one map with handwriting and one without), 1922; 28x48 (Box OV-11, Folder 28)
  - "General Map of the Northern Territory", Australia (one map with handwriting and one without), 1922; 28x48 (Box OV-11, Folder 29)
  - Four Mile Maps of Queensland, Sheet 21A, with Hand-Writing, 1908; 32x42 (Box OV-11, Folder 30)
  - Map of North Pole Entitled "Proposed Route of Wilkins-Ellsworth Trans-Atlantic Submarine Expedition", ca 1931 (Box OV-13, Folder 8)
  - Map: "General Station Locations", Rough Work Map, May 16, 1956 (Box OV-14, Folder 2)
  - Map: "Greenland Research Areas", 1956-1957; 26x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 3)
  - United States Air Force Aeronautical Approach chart of Napasorsuak Fiord, Greenland, May, 1953; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 4)
  - United States Air Force Aeronautical Approach Chart of Narsossuak, Greenland, July, 1953; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 5)
  - World Aeronautical Map of Independence Fjord, Greenland, May, 1951; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 6)
  - United States Air Force Aeronautical Approach chart of Cape Discord, Greenland, April, 1953; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 7)
  - United States Air Force Aeronautical Approach Chart of Syndproven, Greenland, November, 1953; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 8)
  - Map: "Areas characterized by Major Forest Types in the United States", 1949; 44x28 (Box OV-14, Folder 9)
  - Map: "United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey of Alaska" (2 copies), 1954; 18x25 (Box OV-14, Folder 10)
  - Chart: (Blank) Performance Rating Legend: Y-Axis contains rating criteria; X-Axis contains different environmental conditions (roads, precipitations, atmospheric conditions, wind, vegetation). Back side of chart contains rough blueprint sketch, Undated (Box OV-14, Folder 11)
  - World Aeronautical Chart of Robeson Channel, Canada - Greenland, March, 1948; 32x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 15)
  - Map: Northwest Territories - West Sheet of Canada, Undated; 30x17 (Box OV-14, Folder 17)
  - Map: Army Arctic Indoctrination School; Big Delta, Alaska - Quartz Lake and Vicinity, Undated; 42x35 (Box OV-14, Folder 29)
  - Map: Headquarters Army Arctic Indoctrination School - APO 733% Postmaster, Seattle, Washington Overlay A to Accompany Section IV Infantry Battalion in Defense and Attack in the Arctic Map and terrain Exercizes (Quartz Lake and Vicinity), Undated; 19x22 (Box OV-14, Folder 30)
  - Map: Army Arctic Indoctrination School - Big Delta, Alaska - Richardson Highway, Big Delta AFB to Ladd AFB, Undated; 13x27 (Box OV-14, Folder 31)
  - Map: Photographic Index - Quartz Lake and Vicinity, Big Delta, Alaska, October 22, 1949; 22x20 (Box OV-14, Folder 32)
  - Map: World Aeronautical Chart - Gulf of Alaska, March 17, 1948; 22x29 (Box OV-14, Folder 34)
  - Map: Flight Chart - Fairbanks to Kodiak, Alaska, April 1, 1947; 15x44 (Box OV-14, Folder 35)
  - Map of Mackenzie River Delta and Mackenzie Bay, Yukon and Northwest Territories (Canada), 1924; 24x33 (Box OV-20, Folder 1)
  - Carte Synoptiquede L'Hemisphere Nord (North Polar Hemisphere Projection) of altitude, Undated; 28x28 (Box OV-20, Folder 2)
  - Pentagon Shaped Poster - Broken into 10 "Pie" sections with three rectangles overlapping 6 sections, Undated (Box OV-20, Folder 3)
  - Map of Antarctic, Sheet I - American (?) Quadrant (map is torn into two sections with a small top section missing), ca 1929; 32x32 (Box OV-20, Folder 4)
  - Maps of Waterways to Fitzgerald and Fitzgerald to Providence on Front Chipewyan, Resolution, and Hay River Settlement on back, 1931; 26x34 (Box OV-20, Folder 5)
  - Maps of Providence to Camsell Bend and Camsell Bend to Norman on Front Wrigley, Simpson, and Providence on Back, 1931; 26x34 (Box OV-20, Folder 6)
  - "Great Circle Sailing Chart of the North Pacific Ocean", 1922; 40x34 (Box OV-20, Folder 7)
  - Map of Northern and Southern Hemispheres, by National Geographic, 1943; 41x22 (Box OV-20, Folder 8)
  - "The Saros and Metonic Cycles" (chart and diagram), ca 1940s (Box OV-20, Folder 9)
  - Plans of Harbours: Great Slave Lake Canada, 1945; 38x27 (Box S-1, Folder 1)
  - Map: Slave River to Mackenzie River, July, 1943; 42x24 (Box S-1, Folder 2)
  - Map: Norman to Thunder River, 1931; 34x26 (Box S-1, Folder 3)
    Annotated (minor). B&W
  - Map: Mackenzie River to Bering Strait, 1932; 41x27 (Box S-1, Folder 4)
  - Pencil Sketch of "Abstracts" Habitat, Undated (Box S-1, Folder 5)
  - Map: Antarctica and Area, 1955; 34x50 (Box S-1, Folder 6)
  - Map: Antarctica and Area, 1955; 34x50 (Box S-1, Folder 7)
  - Charts: The Arctic Sea North of Canada, National Geographic for Wilkins (3 copies), 1937; 23x16 (Box S-1, Folder 8)
  - AAF Map of the North, January 1945; 35x40 (Box S-1, Folder 9)
  - Hern Hemisphere Chart (3/4), January, 1945; 40x35 (Box S-1, Folder 10)
  - Eurasia Sheet Chart (2/4), January, 1945; 35x41 (Box S-1, Folder 11)
  - AAF Map of the North (4/4): North American Sheet, January, 1945; 35x40 (Box S-1, Folder 12)
  - Northern Hemisphere (Arctic) Wall Planning Chart, Undated; 68x35 (Box S-1, Folder 13)
  - World Map to 60 Degrees South Latitude, July, 1936; 19x19 (Box S-1, Folder 14)
  - Pilot Chart of the Upper Air: North Pacific Ocean, April 1939; 39x27 (Box S-1, Folder 15)
  - Chart: West Coast of Africa: Cuderict Bay to Cape of Good Hope, January, 1929; 31x49 (Box S-1, Folder 16)
  - World Aeronautical Chart: Mt Mckinley Alaska, March 16, 1929; 23x30 (Box S-1, Folder 17)
  - World Aeronautical Chart: Yukon River Alaska, January, 1947; 23x30 (Box S-1, Folder 18)
  - Extended Composite of Aerial Relon Photos, Starts Whitehorse to Northway, 1948 (Box S-1, Folder 19)
  - Chart: Fishers Island Sound, June, 1937; 42x30 (Box S-1, Folder 20)
    Annotated (minor). Color.
  - Chart: Arctic Sea Baffin Bay, September, 1945; 28x20 (Box S-1, Folder 21)
  - Chart: Erebus Bay, June, 1946; 28x21 (Box S-1, Folder 22)
  - Chart: Arctic Sea, Melville Sound, May, 1942; 27x22 (Box S-1, Folder 23)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions, December, 1943; 38x32 (Box S-1, Folder 24)
  - Chart: Plans in Arctic America, June, 1946; 26x21 (Box S-1, Folder 25)
  - Chart: Smith Sound, Kennedy and Robeson Channels, April, 1931; 27x40 (Box S-1, Folder 26)
  - Chart: North Coast of Canada and Arctic Archipelago, April, 1927; 35x41 (Box S-1, Folder 27)
  - Hydrographic Map: The Northwest Hemisphere, Sheet #5, Undated; 60x40 (Box S-1, Folder 28)
  - Position Plotting Sheet: December 1928 30 Position Plotting Sheet, January, 1944; 28x21 (Box S-1, Folder 29)
  - Position Plotting Sheets (2 total), December, 1928; 36x27 (Box S-1, Folder 31)
  - Chart: North American Base Map, June, 1943; 49x35 (Box S-1, Folder 32)
  - Chart: The Northern Hemisphere, 1941; 36x37 (Box S-1, Folder 33)
  - Pilot chart of the Northern Atlantic Ocean, October, 1945; 39x26 (Box S-1, Folder 34)
  - Position Plotting sheets (5 Total), 1939; 35x46 (Box S-1, Folder 35)
  - US Air Force Transportation Chart GH-9, January, 1948; 35x36 (Box S-2, Folder 1)
  - North Coast of Canada and Arctic Archipelago, April, 1927; 40x46 (Box S-2, Folder 2)
  - Northern and Southern Hemispheres Map, April, 1943; 68x36 (Box S-2, Folder 3)
  - Rare 1929 Graf Zeppelin Map, World Flight (Vienna) with Cachet, August, 1929; 29x28 (Box S-2, Folder 4)
  - World Land Areas (map), January, 1954; 18x27 (Box S-2, Folder 5)
  - The World Map, 1943; 48x68 (Box S-2, Folder 6)
  - Chart: The Northern Hemisphere, 1941 (Box S-2, Folder 7)
  - Position Plotting Charts: The Northern Hemisphere (2 total), 1941 (Box S-2, Folder 8)
  - Navigational Chart of the Antarctic (3 total), 1928; 22x22 (Box S-2, Folder 9)
  - Chart: Woods Hole, 1936; 23x16 (Box S-2, Folder 10)
  - Chart: Antarctica, 1943; 33x50 (Box S-2, Folder 11)
  - Map: "Interesting World Map" (no legend), Undated; 44x62 (Box S-2, Folder 12)
  - Map of the Northern Hemisphere, January, 1945; 41x65 (Box S-2, Folder 13)
  - Map: Canada, Alaska, and Greenland, June, 1947; 27x34 (Box S-2, Folder 14)
  - Map: The World (reality series), 1938; 45x57 (Box S-2, Folder 15)
  - Map: Australia and New Zealand, Undated; 50x32 (Box S-2, Folder 16)
  - Map: Pacific Ocean, Undated (Box S-2, Folder 17)
  - Chart: Fairbanks C-5 (Alaska): Chart B-5 attached, 1951; 51x22 (Box S-2, Folder 18)
  - Map: The Northern Hemisphere, 1946; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Planning Chart: Northern Hemisphere (SP-2), 1943; 27x49 (Box S-2, Folder 20)
  - North America - Far East (SP-2, Sheet 2), Undated; 27x49 (Box S-2, Folder 21)
  - Chart: World Weather Extremes, May, 1955; 8x14 (Box S-2, Folder 22)
  - Chart: World Weather Extremes, 1956; 8x13 (Box S-2, Folder 23)
  - Chart: Global Mean Temperatures January, January, 1958; 11x20 (Box S-2, Folder 24)
  - Chart: Global Mean Temperatures July, January, 1958; 11x20 (Box S-2, Folder 25)
  - Set of Three Schematic Cross-Sections of African Vegetation (In French), Undated (Box S-2, Folder 26)
  - Topo Map: Fairbanks D-3, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 27)
  - Topo Map: Big Delta A-4, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 28)
  - Topo Map: Fairbanks D-2, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 29)
  - Topo Map: Big Delta A-5, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 30)
  - Topo Map: Big Delta B-4 Alaska, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 31)
  - Topo Map: Big Delta B-5 Alaska, 1951; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 32)
  - Physical Relief Chary GH-2 Northern Hemistphere, August, 1946; 38x36 (Box S-2, Folder 33)
  - Blue Line World Map, Undated; 30x40 (Box S-2, Folder 34)
  - Canada Department of Mines and Resources "Northern Hemisphere" Map, 1941; 37x37 (Box S-2, Folder 35)
  - Wall Hanging Map of Western canada, 1937 (Box S-2, Folder 36)
  - Economic Chart GH-8, Northern Hemisphere, August, 1946; 36x38 (Box S-2, Folder 37)
  - AAF Strategic Outline Chart SO-16 Northern Hemisphere, 1946; 36x38 (Box S-2, Folder 38)
  - Climatic Chart GM-5, Northern Hemisphere, 1946; 38x36 (Box S-2, Folder 39)
  - Annual Precipitation Chart GH-4, Northern Hemisphere, August, 1946; 38x36 (Box S-2, Folder 40)
  - Canada Department of Mines and Resources "Northern Hemisphere" (with pencil alterations), 1941; 37x37 (Box S-2, Folder 41)
  - Canada Department of Mines and Resources "Northern Hemisphere" (with pencil alterations), 1941; 37x37 (Box S-2, Folder 42)
  - Pictorial Map of the "Republic of Panama and Canal Zone", Undated; 37x48 (Box S-2, Folder 43)
  - World Aeronautical Chart: Panama Canal, 1952; 22x29 (Box S-2, Folder 44)
  - National Geographic Magazine Map: "The Arctic Regions", 1925; 19x20 (Box S-2, Folder 45)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 46)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 47)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 48)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 49)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 50)
  - Chart: The Arctic Regions (US Navy), September, 1937; 38x32 (Box S-2, Folder 51)
  - The Arctic Sea of North Canada: Line Maps Prepared by National Geographic for Wilkins (set of 6, various pencil markings), August, 1937; 16x23 (Box S-2, Folder 52)
  - Circumpolar Northern Hemisphere, Meteorological Base Map, 1922 (Box S-2, Folder 53)
  - Set 54 of Northern Hemisphere Arctic Charts (7), Undated, ca 1940s; 54x34 (Box S-2, Folder 54)
  - Charts: "From the Hydrographic Office to the Arctic Section - Weather Bureau (sealed in brown wrapping), Undated; 44x42 (Box S-2, Folder 55)
  - Chart: Alaska, Clothing Requirement Areas, Undated; 20x26 (Box S-3, Folder 1)
  - World Atlas of Sea Surface Temperatures, 1944 (Box S-3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Northern Hemisphere: North of 39 degrees 30' showing topography, January, 1945; 39x73 (Box S-3, Folder 3)
  - Antarctica, March, 1943; 33x50 (Box S-3, Folder 4)
  - Index of Aerial Photographs: Alaska, Alaskan Railway System (4 total), Undated (Box S-3, Folder 5)
  - Natsek Cove: Greenland-East Coast, February, 1943; 19x21 (Box S-3, Folder 6)
  - Siglu Fjord to Njardvik, June, 1930; 27x40 (Box S-3, Folder 7)
  - Chart: Prestbakkaey to Bordeyri, March, 1941; 21x28 (Box S-3, Folder 8)
  - Chart: North Cape to Siglu Fjord, Iceland, December, 1942; 27x4 (Box S-3, Folder 9)
  - Chart: Hesteyri Fjord, Iceland, 1945; 22x29 (Box S-3, Folder 10)
  - Chart: Plans on the Northwest Coast of Iceland, 1945; 28x42 (Box S-3, Folder 11)
  - Chart: Snaefellsjokull to North Cape, Iceland, 1930; 24x40 (Box S-3, Folder 12)
  - Chart: Hvalfjordur and Borgarfjordur, Iceland, 1941; 21x22 (Box S-3, Folder 13)
  - Chart to Hafnarjordr and Reykjavik, Iceland, 1939; 42x30 (Box S-3, Folder 14)
  - Portland to Snaefelljokull Including Faxafloi, Iceland, 1932; 30x42 (Box S-3, Folder 15)
  - Chart: Iceland, 1942; 30x42 (Box S-3, Folder 16)
  - Chart: Reydar and Faskrud Fjords, Iceland, June, 1943; 28x40 (Box S-3, Folder 17)
  - Chart: Stokksnes to Portland, Iceland, May, 1940; 30x42 (Box S-3, Folder 18)
  - Chart: Beru Fjord, Iceland, 1943; 30x42 (Box S-3, Folder 19)
  - Chart: The Greenland and Barents Seas, 1944; 36x46 (Box S-3, Folder 20)
  - Chart: Upernivik, Greenland, 1941; 23x26 (Box S-3, Folder 21)
  - Chart: Smith Sound, Kennedy and Robeson Channels, 1940; 30x42 (Box S-3, Folder 22)
  - ChartL Greenland West Coast, Prince Regents Bay, 1941; 18x29 (Box S-3, Folder 23)
  - Chart: Greenland West Coast: Murchison Sound to Wolstenholme Fjord, 1941; 21x29 (Box S-3, Folder 24)
  - Chart: Greenland West Coast, Wolstenholme I to Concial Rock, 1941; 20x30 (Box S-3, Folder 25)
  - Chart: Danmark Harbor and Environs, Greenland, 1942; 20x22 (Box S-3, Folder 26)
  - Charts: Preliminary Information Bloomsterbugden, 1942 Preliminary Survey Solitoerbugt Ello O Greenland, 36x25 (Box S-3, Folder 27)
  - Chart: Berg Fjord, greenland, 1942; 27x36 (Box S-3, Folder 28)
  - Chart: Bessel Fjord, Greenland, 1942; 25x35 (Box S-3, Folder 29)
  - Chart: Dyra Fjord, Iceland, 1941; 21x27 (Box S-3, Folder 30)
  - Chart: Danmark Havn, Northeast Greenland, 1942; 19x24 (Box S-3, Folder 31)
  - Chart: Njardvik to Stokksnes, Iceland, 1942; 20x27 (Box S-3, Folder 32)
  - Chart: Eyia Fjord, Iceland, 1942; 22x28 (Box S-3, Folder 33)
  - Chart: Plans on East Coast of Iceland, Horne Fiord, Nord, Hellis, and Vid Fiords, 1940; 21x27 (Box S-3, Folder 34)
  - Charts: Aeronautical Edition, St. Elias, Yukon, 1948 Aeronautical Edition, Whitehorse-Teslin, Yukon Territory, Undated; 52x42 (Box S-3, Folder 35)
  - Julianhaab Sheet: Greenland, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 1)
  - Egedeminde, Greenland, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 2)
  - Kusanartok Harbor, Cape Adelaer, Greenland, 1944 (Box S-4a, Folder 3)
  - Hudson Strait Sheet, Canada, 1944 (Box S-4a, Folder 4)
  - Koojesse Inlet, Upper Frobisher Bay, Canada, 1943 (Box S-4a, Folder 5)
  - Coral Harbour, Southampton Island, Canada, 1943 (Box S-4a, Folder 6)
  - Upernivik-Etah, Greenland, 1942 (Box S-4a, Folder 7)
  - Smith Sound, Kennedy and Robeson Channels, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 8)
  - Greenland West Coast, Murchison Sound to Wolstenholme Fjord, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 9)
  - North Atlantic Ocean, Northern Sheet, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 10)
  - Newfoundland to the British Islands including Southern Greenland and Iceland, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 11)
  - Grand Banks to Davis Strait, 1941 (Box S-4a, Folder 12)
  - St Lewis Sound and Inlet, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 13)
  - Coast of Labrador, North America, 1934 (Box S-4a, Folder 14)
  - North and East Coasts of Newfoundland and the Strait of Belle Isle, North America, 1934 (Box S-4a, Folder 15)
  - Boulder Rock to Domino Run, Coast of Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 16)
  - Anchorages on the Northeast Coast of Labrador, 1913 (Box S-4a, Folder 17)
  - Caoe Greep to Cape Porcupine, Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 18)
  - Domino Run, Coast of Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 19)
  - Sandwich Bay to Nain including Hamilton Inlet, Coast of Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 20)
  - Entrance to Hamilton Inlet and Adjacent Harbours, Labrador, 1944 (Box S-4a, Folder 21)
  - Jeanette Bay to Tuchialik Bay including Webeck Harbo, Labrador, 1944 (Box S-4a, Folder 22)
  - Plans of Anchorages on NE Coast of Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 23)
  - Approaches to Nain and Port Manvers, Labrador, 1940 (Box S-4a, Folder 24)
  - Cape Mugford Area, Labrador, 1945 (Box S-4a, Folder 25)
  - Cape Chidley Sheet, Labrador, 1944 (Box S-4b, Folder 26)
  - Nachvak Bay to Saglek Bay Entrance, Labrador, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 27)
  - Saglek Bay to Hebron Fjord, Labrador, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 28)
  - Bartlett Narrows, Upper Frobisher Bay, Canada, 1944 (Box S-4b, Folder 29)
  - Frobisher Bay, Canada, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 30)
  - Cape Chidley Area, Labrador, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 31)
  - Eclipse Harbor to Cape White Handkerchief, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 32)
  - Northwestern Part of Frobisher Bay, Canada, 1944 (Box S-4b, Folder 33)
  - Cape Dier to Cape Searle, Baffin Island, Canada, 1944 (Box S-4b, Folder 34)
  - Cincinnati Press Channel, Upper Probisher Bay, Canada, 1943 (Box S-4b, Folder 35)